Edward L. Bernays Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: General Correspondence, 1913-1963 (Box I:4-55)
  - 1913-1943 (Box I:4)
    - Manassas Industrial School for Colored Youth, Manassas, Va., 1922
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1913-1924, (7 folders)
      - 1921-1932, (16 folders) (Box I:6)
      - 1931-1946, (10 folders) (Box I:7)
    - One day conference re social welfare, New York, N.Y., 1943, (2 folders)
    - Prospective clients, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box I:8)
    - Public relations fellowship, 1943, (2 folders)
    - "R" miscellaneous, 1921-1924, (2 folders)
    - Real property, 1931-1941, (5 folders)
    - Rotary Club, 1920-1921
    - Sprague, O. M. W., luncheon, 1934
    - "Stage Fright," 1925
    - Survey on war in textbooks, 1935
    - Thirsen, J. Mitchell, 1924
    - Unemployment, 1922
    - "V-W" miscellaneous, 1923-1924
    - Weigand, Karl, luncheon, 1932
  - 1944 (Box I:9)
    - Awards
    - "B-C" miscellaneous
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.
    - Cushman, Robert E. (Box I:10)
    - "D-M" miscellaneous
    - "N-R" miscellaneous (Box I:11)
    - Real property
    - "S-V" miscellaneous
    - War loan campaign
    - "Z" miscellaneous
  - 1945 (Box I:12)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - American Red Cross
    - Awards
    - "B" miscellaneous
    - Bender, Robert J.
    - Boomer, Lucius
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Collier, John
    - Crank letters
    - "D-E" miscellaneous
    - Encomiums
    - "F" miscellaneous (Box I:13)
    - Financial statements
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Geddes, Norman Bel
    - "H-I" miscellaneous
    - Independent Citizens' Committee
    - Jewish affairs
    - Joint Coffee Promotion Committee
    - "K" miscellaneous
    - Karelsen, Frank
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Labor unions
    - Luce, Henry Robinson
    - "M-O" miscellaneous
    - Odum, Howard
    - Otis, Elizabeth
    - "P" miscellaneous (Box I:14)
    - Public education
    - Public opinion newsletter
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Rachmaninoff fund
    - "S" miscellaneous
    - State Department proposal
    - "U-V" miscellaneous
    - Veterans
    - "W-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1946 (Box I:15)
    - "A-C" miscellaneous
    - Awards
    - Bender, Robert J.
    - Bilbo, Theodore G.
    - Citizens' Planning Committee
    - "D-F" miscellaneous
    - Financial statements
    - Fuld, Stanley H.
    - "G-I" miscellaneous
    - Institute of World Control of Atomic Energy
    - "J-K" miscellaneous
    - Lee, Atherton
    - "M-O" miscellaneous
    - New York Public Library, New York, N.Y.
    - "P-R" miscellaneous
    - Radio broadcasts
    - "S-Z" miscellaneous
    - Wickware, Francis S.
    - Wilson, Charles M.
    - World governments
  - 1947 (Box I:16)
    - "A-B" miscellaneous
    - Advertisement, New York Times
    - Buffalo, N.Y.
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.
    - "D-F" miscellaneous
    - Financial statements
    - "G-M" miscellaneous
    - March of Time
    - "N-P" miscellaneous
    - New York Public Library, New York, N.Y.
    - "Q-R" miscellaneous
    - Roosevelt College, Chicago, Ill.
    - "S-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1948 (Box I:17)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Abbott, Mary S.
    - Air Products
    - Army Industrial College, Washington, D.C.
    - Awards
    - "B-C" miscellaneous
    - Contact
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.
    - Crowell, Merle
    - "D-F" miscellaneous
    - Financial statements
    - "G-K" miscellaneous
    - "L" miscellaneous (Box I:18)
    - "Lend an Ear"
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - Mason, Gregory
    - Mencken, H. L.
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - New York Herald Tribune
    - New York University, New York, N.Y.
    - "O-P" miscellaneous
    - Public relations
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Radcliffe College, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Rinehart & Co.
    - Roelofs, Richard, Jr.
    - "S" miscellaneous
    - Samstag, Nicholas
    - Tead, Ordway
    - "W" miscellaneous
  - 1949 (Box I:19)
    - "A-B" miscellaneous
    - "At War With the Army"
    - Bibliography about Bernays
    - British Museum, London, England
    - "C-D" miscellaneous
    - European trip
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Financial statements
    - Funke, Lewis
    - "G-H" miscellaneous
    - Gale, D. M.
    - Goldsmith, Arthur
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - House Magazine Institute
    - "I-L" miscellaneous
    - London, England, trip
    - "M-N" miscellaneous
    - New York University, New York, N.Y., professorship
    - "O-R" miscellaneous
    - "S" miscellaneous (Box I:20)
    - Solon, Lawrence
    - "T-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1950
    - Advertisement, New York Times
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y. (Box I:21)
    - Hall of Fame, New York University, New York, N.Y., survey
  - 1951
    - Bibliography about Bernays
    - Financial statements
    - Public relations survey
  - 1952 (Box I:22)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Abbott, Mary S.
    - American Civil Liberties Union
    - Auchincloss, Douglas
    - "B" miscellaneous
    - Benton, William
    - Bradley, Glenn P.
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Citizens' Union of the City of New York
    - City Center of Music and Drama, New York, N.Y.
    - Clark, Marguerite
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
    - Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion
      - New York, N.Y.
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.
    - "D-F" miscellaneous
    - Financial statements
    - "G-H" miscellaneous (Box I:23)
    - Hellman, Geoffrey
    - "I-L" miscellaneous
    - Lottinville, Savoie
    - "M-N" miscellaneous
    - New Leader
    - "O" miscellaneous (Box I:24)
    - Opportunity
    - Otis, Elizabeth
    - Overseas Press Club
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Page, David
    - Printers' Ink
    - Promotion letters
      - Advertising agency executives
      - Business executives
      - Consultant management engineers
      - Former clients
      - Miscellaneous
      - Printers' Ink advertisers
      - Sales executives
    - "Q-R" miscellaneous
    - "S" miscellaneous (Box I:25)
    - Samstag, Nicholas
    - Stevenson, Adlai E. (1900-1965)
    - Stith, Mary E.
    - "T-V" miscellaneous
    - United Nations' World
    - "W" miscellaneous
    - Werner, William G.
    - "X-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1953 (Box I:26)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - American Civil Liberties Union
    - "Author Meets the Critic" program
    - "B" miscellaneous
    - Baggett, S. G.
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Cahn, Julius O. W.
    - Capehart, Homer E.
    - Clark, Marguerite
    - Cominsky, Jack
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - English-Speaking Union of the United States
    - "E-F" miscellaneous
    - Financial statements
    - "G" miscellaneous (Box I:27)
    - Gimbel, Bernard F.
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - Herndon, Richard
    - Holthusen, Henry
    - "I-J" miscellaneous
    - Jones, Ernest
    - Lottinville, Savoie
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - MacGovern, James
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - National Planning Association
    - Nursing homes
    - "O" miscellaneous (Box I:28)
    - Otis, Elizabeth
    - Overseas Press Club
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Partridge, Russell G.
    - Promotion letters
      - Business executives
      - Hotel executives
      - Lawyers
      - Millionaires of advertising
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Ross, Stanley
    - "S" miscellaneous (Box I:29)
    - Samstag, Nicholas
    - Saturday Review of Literature
    - Strategic intelligence
    - "T-W" miscellaneous
    - Werner, William G.
    - Whitman, Ann
    - "X-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1954 (Box I:30)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Adult Education Association
    - "B-C" miscellaneous
    - Cahn, Julius W.
    - Clarke, Marguerite
    - Cominsky, Jack
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.
    - "D-E" miscellaneous
    - Educational Institute of the Air, New York, N.Y.
    - English-Speaking Union of the United States
    - "F-G" miscellaneous (Box I:31)
    - Gross, Ernest
    - "H-J" miscellaneous
    - Jones, Ernest
    - "K-L" miscellaneous
    - Levitas, Sol M.
    - Lottinville, Savoie
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - Marvin, Burton W.
    - "N-O" miscellaneous (Box I:32)
    - Otis, Elizabeth
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Page, David
    - "Q-R" miscellaneous
    - Ruggles, William B.
    - "S" miscellaneous
    - Trailer Coach Manufacturers' Association
    - "U-V" miscellaneous
    - Variety
    - "W" miscellaneous
    - Wise, Ethel
    - "X-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1955 (Box I:33)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - All-day neighborhood schools
    - "B" miscellaneous
    - Burnett, Leo
    - "C-G" miscellaneous
    - Gross, Ernest
    - "H-P" miscellaneous
    - New Hampshire trip
    - Otis, Elizabeth
    - Public School No. 184, New York, N.Y., class reunion
    - Reporter
    - "S-T" miscellaneous
    - Schuster, Max
    - Twenty leading Americans survey
  - 1956 (Box I:34)
    - "A-I" miscellaneous
    - Jones, Ernest
    - "K-L" miscellaneous
    - Leigh, Colston W.
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - Modern opera
    - "N-S" miscellaneous
    - Spanel, A. N.
    - "T-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1957 (Box I:35)
    - "A-C" miscellaneous
    - Cowen, Myron M.
    - "D-L" miscellaneous
    - Letters Abroad
    - "M" miscellaneous (Box I:36)
    - Maguire, Jeremiah D.
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - National Commission on Literacy
    - "O-S" miscellaneous
    - Spanel, A. N.
    - Spivak, Lawrence E.
    - "T-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1958 (Box I:37)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Advisory Commission on the Performing Arts
    - "B-C" miscellaneous
    - Cowen, Myron M.
    - "D-F" miscellaneous
    - Faulkner, Alexander H.
    - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies
    - Freedom of Information Center, University of Missouri, Columbia, Mo.
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - "H-J" miscellaneous (Box I:38)
    - Japan
    - "K-M" miscellaneous
    - Martin, William M., Jr.
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - "O" miscellaneous (Box I:39)
    - Overseas Press Club
    - "P-R" miscellaneous
    - Real estate property
    - "S" miscellaneous
    - Spivak, Lawrence E.
    - "T-W" miscellaneous
    - Wortham, Howard F.
    - "X-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1959 (Box I:40)
    - "A-C" miscellaneous
    - Citizens' Committee for Public Schools, New York, N.Y.
    - Conference on Distribution, Boston, Mass.
    - Cutlip, Scott M.
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - "Dime Novels"
    - "E-H" miscellaneous
    - Humphrey, Hubert H.
    - Independent Citizens' Committee for Amendment Four
    - "J" miscellaneous
    - "K" miscellaneous (Box I:41)
    - Kerrison, Irvine L.
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Letters Abroad
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - Mayers, Henry
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - New York Times, special supplement, (3 folders); (7 folders) (Box I:42)
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - "Open End" broadcasts
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Printers' Ink
    - "Q-R" miscellaneous
    - Real property (Box I:43)
    - "S" miscellaneous
    - Scholastic
    - Shakespeare in Central Park, New York, N.Y.
    - "T-U" miscellaneous
    - United States Information Agency
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Vision
    - "W-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1960 (Box I:44)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Arden House, Arden, N.Y.
    - "B" miscellaneous
    - Business leaders survey
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
    - Cutlip, Scott M.
    - "D-F" miscellaneous
    - "G-H" miscellaneous (Box I:45)
    - How to Be a Live American
    - "I-L" miscellaneous
    - Letters Abroad
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - Mayers, Henry
    - "N-O" miscellaneous
    - "Open End" broadcasts
    - "P" miscellaneous (Box I:46)
    - Philippe, Claudius C.
    - "R" miscellaneous
    - Real estate property
    - "S" miscellaneous
    - Sagendorph, Robb
    - Shakespeare in Central Park, New York, N.Y.
    - "T-W" miscellaneous
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, Washington, D.C.
    - "X-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1961 (Box I:47)
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Advertising Federation of America's Conference, Washington, D.C.
    - Arden House, Arden, N.Y.
    - "B" miscellaneous
    - Ballou, Robert O.
    - Baumgartner, Leona
    - Birthday greetings
    - Book orders
    - "C" miscellaneous (Box I:48)
    - Chesley, Willoughby S.
    - Citizens' Committee for the Rockefeller Foundation
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
    - Commerce Department
    - Cutlip, Scott M.
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Employment applications
    - "F" miscellaneous (Box I:49)
    - "A Far Country"
    - Follow-ups
    - Foundation for Research in Human Behavior
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Gould House symposium, New York University, New York, N.Y.
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - "I" miscellaneous
    - Invitations
    - "J-M" miscellaneous (Box I:50)
    - Mayers, Henry
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Naval War College, Newport, R.I.
    - New York Public Library, New York, N.Y.
    - New York Philharmonic Orchestra
    - Newspaper survey, (6 folders); (11 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:51, Box I:52)
    - Northwestern University, Evanston, Ill.
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Overseas Press Club
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Public relations
    - "R" miscellaneous (Box I:53)
    - Richards Rosen Press
    - "S" miscellaneous
    - Shakespeare in Central Park, New York, N.Y.
    - "T-U" miscellaneous
    - United States Information Agency
    - "W" miscellaneous
    - Wagner, Robert F.
    - "X-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1962 (Box I:54)
    - "A-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1963
    - American surveys
    - Book orders
    - Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen
    - Chesley, Willoughby S.
    - Educational activities
    - Employment applications
    - Financial statements
    - Foreign affairs
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Invitations
    - Miscellany
    - New York State Department of Education (Box I:55)
    - Office supplies
    - Pace College, New York, N.Y.
    - Peace Research Institute
    - Real estate property
    - Requests for information
    - Suffolk University, Boston, Mass., lectures
    - Walker, Harry
- Part I: Client, Institution, and Organization File, 1916-1964 (Box I:56-421)
  Correspondence, memoranda, printed matter, reports, surveys, newspaper clippings, financial papers, photographs, lists, press releases, and notes.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of person, organization, or topic and therein chronologically, except for the Procter & Gamble Co. file which is arranged alphabetically.
  - Acoustic Products Co., 1927-1932 (Box I:56)
  - Actors' Equity Association, 1960
  - Actors' Fund of America, 1919
  - Aeolian Co., 1927-1929
  - A. G. Spalding and Brothers See Container I:342, Spalding and Brothers
  - Alexander, Robert J., 1923
  - Allerton House Corp., 1923
  - Allied Chemical & Dye Corp., 1933 (Box I:57)
  - America Self-Contained Committee (Box I:58)
    - 1933
      - Jan.-Oct.
      - Nov. (Box I:59)
      - Dec. (Box I:60)
    - 1934 (Box I:61)
      - Jan.
      - Feb. (Box I:62)
      - Mar. (Box I:63)
      - Apr.-June (Box I:64)
      - July-Dec. (Box I:65)
    - 1935
      - Jan.-Mar.
      - Apr.-Dec. (Box I:66)
    - 1936 (Box I:67)
  - American Academy of Pediatrics, 1946 (Box I:68)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1938
  - American Booksellers' Association, 1924
  - American Clinica, 1942-1943
  - American Distilling Co., 1933
  - American Economic Foundation, 1935
  - American Federation of Radio Artists 1949-1950
  - American Hebrew and Jewish Tribune, 1932
  - American Hotel Association, undated
  - American Institute of Baking, 1942-1943
  - American Jewish Committee, 1938
  - American Journal of Nursing, 1945-1946
  - American Library Association, 1956 (Box I:69)
  - American Nurses Association (Box I:70)
    - 1946-1949, (3 folders); (13 folders) (Box I:71)
    - 1947 (Box I:72)
    - 1948 (Box I:73)
      - Jan.-Apr.
      - May-June (Box I:74)
      - July-Aug. (Box I:75)
      - Sept. (Box I:76)
      - Oct. (Box I:77)
      - Nov. (Box I:78)
      - Dec. (Box I:79)
    - 1949
      - Jan.
      - Feb.-Apr. (Box I:80)
  - American Optometric Association, 1941-1945, 1962 (Box I:81)
  - American Photographic Service Bureau, 1927
  - American Radiator Co., 1930, (16 folders); (6 folders) (Box I:82, Box I:83)
  - American Road Builders Association, 1941-1942
  - American Safety Razor Corp., 1929
  - American Tobacco Co. (Box I:84)
    - 1926-1931
    - 1928-1931 (Box I:85)
    - 1929-1932 (Box I:86)
    - 1929 (Box I:87)
      - Jan.-Mar.
      - Apr.-Dec. (Box I:88)
    - 1930 (Box I:89)
      - Jan.-May
      - June-Dec. (Box I:90)
    - 1931 (Box I:91)
      - Jan.-Feb.
      - Mar.-May (Box I:92)
      - June-July (Box I:93)
      - July-Aug. (Box I:94)
      - Sept.-Dec. (Box I:95)
    - 1932 (Box I:96)
    - 1933 (Box I:97)
    - 1934 (Box I:98)
      - Jan.-Feb.
      - Mar.-May (Box I:99)
      - June-Dec. (Box I:100)
    - 1935-1936 (Box I:101)
  - American Watch Assemblers' Association, 1943-1945 (Box I:102)
  - Ansco Photo Products, 1927
  - Apple Blossom Festival, Kingston, N.Y., 1938
  - Arrowhead Hot Springs, Calif., 1947
  - Art Lamp Manufacturing Co., 1926-1927
  - Arthritis and Rheumatism Foundation (Box I:103)
    - 1956-1957
    - 1957-1961 (Box I:104)
  - Artists for Victory, 1943-1944 (Box I:105)
  - Association of Actors and Artists of America, 1949-1950
  - Automobile Manufacturers' Association, 1938
  - Aviation Corp. of America, 1932-1933
  - Babies' Hospital of the City of New York, New York, N.Y., 1921
  - Bailey Brothers, 1923
  - Ballet Theater, 1946 (Box I:106)
  - Ballets russes See Container I:150, Diaghileff Ballets Russes
  - Bank of America (Box I:107)
    - 1938-1939
    - 1939 (Box I:108)
    - 1939-1940 (Box I:109)
  - Barrett Co. (Box I:110)
    - 1933-1934, 1940-1945
    - 1938-1939 (Box I:111)
    - 1939 (Box I:112)
  - Beechnut Packing Co., 1925 (Box I:113)
  - Benedetti, René, 1921-1922
  - Benedict, Agnes E., 1941-1942
  - Bermuda, undated
  - Bern, Paul, 1925
  - Best Foods, Inc., 1926-1927
  - Bird Cage Co., 1949-1950
  - Blackman Co., 1931
  - Blumenthal Co., 1928-1929, (15 folders); (16 folders) (Box I:114, Box I:115)
  - Bock Co., 1932-1933 (Box I:116)
  - Bolton, Frances Payne Bingham (Box I:117)
    - 1941-1955
    - 1953 (Box I:118)
    - 1954 (Box I:119)
  - Boni & Liveright, 1919-1926 (Box I:120)
  - Book Publishers Research Institute
    - 1930, (8 folders); (13 folders); (14 folders) (Box I:121, Box I:122)
    - 1930-1931 (Box I:123)
  - Book-Cadillac Hotel, Detroit, Mich., 1925 (Box I:124)
  - Bourjois, Inc., 1923-1925
  - Brant & Brant, 1927-1928
  - Brant & Kirkpatrick, 1920
  - Brooklyn Daily Eagle, 1934
  - Brooklyn-Manhattan Transit System, New York, N.Y., 1937
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1963-1964 (Box I:125)
  - Brown Durell Co., 1926
  - Brunswick-Balke-Collendar Co., 1925
  - Bureau for Musical Service, 1927
  - Business Builders, 1921-1922
  - Calderone, Frank A., 1955-1956 (Box I:126)
  - California Survey Corp., 1952
  - Camillus Cutlery Co., 1950, 1956
  - Cardiac Committee, 1920-1921 (Box I:127)
  - Carnegie Hall Corp.
    - 1960-1961
    - 1961-1962 (Box I:128)
  - Cartier (Box I:129)
    - 1921-1929
    - 1922-1930 (Box I:130)
    - 1925-1931 (Box I:131)
  - Case Co., 1937 (Box I:132)
  - Celanese Corp. of America, 1929
  - Central Savings Bank, 1933
  - Cheney Brothers (Box I:133)
    - 1923-1927
    - 1926-1928 (Box I:134)
  - Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1929-1930 (Box I:135)
  - Citizens' Budget Commission, 1923, 1931-32
  - City Stores Mercantile Co., 1934
  - Citywide Citizens' Committee on Harlem, 1942
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1929-1930
  - Columbia University, New York, N.Y., 1950-1951
  - Columbian Rope Co. (Box I:136)
    - 1947
      - Jan.-June
      - July-Sept. (Box I:137)
      - Oct. (Box I:138)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box I:139)
      - Dec. (Box I:140)
    - 1948 (Box I:141)
      - Jan.
      - Feb.-Apr. (Box I:142)
      - May (Box I:143)
  - Committee for Consumer Legislation, 1934 (Box I:144)
  - Committee for Modern Zoning, 1960, (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box I:145)
  - Committee on Publicity Methods in Social Work, 1926-1927
  - Committee on the Cost of Medical Care, 1931-1932 (Box I:146)
  - Community Chest, 1931
  - Condé Nast Publications, 1930-1931 (Box I:147)
  - Continental Baking Co., 1925
  - Cosmopolitan, 1921-1922 (Box I:148)
  - Council for Democracy, 1941
  - Countess Mara, Inc., 1945
  - Creange, Henry, 1925-1928 (Box I:149)
  - Credit Union National Association, 1955
  - Crowther, Samuel, 1934
  - Curtis Publishing Co., 1932, (5 folders); (7 folders) (Box I:150)
  - DeForest, Robert, 1929
  - Diaghileff Ballets Russes, 1915-1916
  - Diamond, Milton, 1942-1943
  - Dodge Brothers (Box I:151)
    - 1927
    - 1928 (Box I:152)
    - 1928 (Box I:153)
      - Jan.-June
      - Feb.-May (Box I:154)
      - Mar.-June (Box I:155)
      - May-Dec. (Box I:156)
    - 1928-1929 (Box I:157)
    - 1929 (Box I:158)
    - 1929-1930, 1938 (Box I:159)
  - Dort Motor Co., 1921 (Box I:160)
  - Downtown Businessmen's Association, undated
  - Duncan, Anna, 1927
  - Durant Motors, Inc., 1929
  - East Orange, N.J., 1958-1960 (Box I:161)
  - Eastern Millinery Association, 1925 (Box I:162)
  - Edible Gelatin Manufacturers Association, 1924-1927
  - Edison Splitdorf Co., 1928
  - Egert Research Corp., 1945
  - Electronic Exhibitors, 1940
  - Elkus, Abram I., 1920
  - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corp., 1953
  - Fidelity and Deposit Co. of Maryland, 1925-1926
  - Filene, E. A. (Box I:163)
    - 1927-1929
    - 1930-1931 (Box I:164)
    - 1930 (Box I:165)
      - Jan.-June
      - Apr.-Dec. (Box I:166)
      - Oct. (Box I:167)
    - 1931
      - Jan.
      - Jan.-Apr. (Box I:168)
  - Fish and Seafood Institute, 1935 (Box I:169)
  - Flannigan, James R., 1948 (Box I:170)
  - Flotil Products Corp., 1947-1950
  - Fokine, Michael and Vera, 1919-1920
  - Folding Paper Box Association of America, 1954
  - Food Education Bureau, 1927-1928
  - Foreign Woods Committee, 1930
  - Fortune magazine
    - 1937, (4 folders); (9 folders) (Box I:171)
    - 1937-1938 (Box I:172)
  - Foundation for Research on Human Behavior, 1957
  - Frankl Galleries, 1938 (Box I:173)
  - Franklin Institute, Philadelphia, Pa.
    - 1941-1942
    - 1943-1944 (Box I:174)
  - French Day Nursery, New York, N.Y., 1920-1922
  - French Industrial Exposition, Paris, France, 1924-1925
  - Friends of Danish Freedom and Democracy, 1940
  - F. W. Woolworth Co., 1936-1937
  - Gantner & Mattern Co., 1947
  - Gartner & Bender, 1947 (Box I:175)
  - Gasoline Manufacturers Pump Association, undated
  - Geddes, Norman Bel, 1944-1945
  - General Food Corp., 1942
  - General Mills, Inc., 1948
  - General Motors Corp.
    - 1932-1933, (16 folders); (13 folders) (Box I:176)
    - 1933-1934 (Box I:177)
  - Goldenberg, Inc., 1948 (Box I:178)
  - Goldman, Eric Frederic, 1946-1950
  - Goldman, Sachs & Co., 1944 (Box I:179)
  - Goldwyn, Samuel, 1920
  - Good Housekeeping, 1920-1921
  - Grainger, Percy, 1917
  - Grauer, Ben, 1950 (Box I:180)
  - Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., 1931-1933
  - Great Northern Railway, 1935-1936 (Box I:181)
  - Greater New York Real Estate Bondholders' Committee, 1932
  - Greeting Card Industry Committee, 1941-1945 (Box I:182)
  - Grossman, Albert, 1926-1927
  - Habima Theater, 1927 (Box I:183)
  - Hairdressers' Association, 1924
  - Hampshire House, 1931
  - Hart, Schaffner & Marx, 1925
  - Hartol Products, 1934-1935
  - Harvitt, Henry G., 1921-1922 (Box I:184)
  - Havana Cigar Industry, 1932-1935
  - Heifetz, Jascha, 1937
  - Herman Shoe Co.
    - 1926
      - Feb.-Sept.
      - Apr. (Box I:185)
      - Apr. (Box I:186)
      - Apr.-Sept. (Box I:187)
  - Herndon & Pangborn, 1931
  - Heyman, Donald M., 1931
  - Hillman Foundation, 1938
  - Hillside Housing Corp. (Box I:188)
    - 1932-1933
    - 1933 (Box I:189)
    - 1933 (Box I:190)